JONEER

ABOUT ME

Along with my professional & open-source experience with software engineering, I also bring a well-rounded educational foundation with a BS in Full-Stack Web Development (4.0 GPA) and a Certificate of Full-Stack Web Development from a bootcamp. I also bring the soft-skills to integrate into any team.

EXPERIENCE

FARM BUREAU BANK

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Responsible for the development and maintenance of internal and external web applications and tools. Writes, tests, develops and implements custom programs to streamline financial institution workflows. Tech: jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL May 2019 - Present

CNF TECHNOLOGIES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Responsible for developing and maintaining the full stack of a website utilized by the U.S. Air Force to maintain and track data on cryptographic products. Tech: ASP.NET, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL DataTables, Bootbox, Font Awesome & Bootstrap. Mar - Dec 2018

VARIOUS ORGANIZATIONS

OPEN SOURCE SOFTWARE CONTRIBUTOR

Develops and delivers software solutions to over 20 organizations including The Apache Software Foundation, Mozilla, #VetsWhoCode, Microsoft & more. Tech: React, Docker, C#, Node.js, EJS, Tailwind CSS, Markdown, Git, Angular, JavaScript, JSON. Oct 2016 - Present

U.S. ARMY

SOLDIER

Planned, coordinated, and conducted training events in order to prepare for deploying into permissive and non-permissive environments. Trained and led teams, as Senior Enlisted Advisor and Medical Provider, on multiple deployments. Sep 2001 - Nov 2016

CONTACT

kevinjones.engineer github.com/joneskj55 linkedin.com/in/joneskj55 joneskj55@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY

2020 - 2022 | BS Web Development

CODEUP

2016 - 2017 | Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

SKILLS

JavaScript Git
HTML CSS
Node.js React
Angular Java
Express ASP.NET
MongoDB SQL